<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- information on the copying conditions. -->
    <string name="app_name">ooniprobe</string>
    <string name="testing_history">Tests</string>
    <string name="select_test">Select test</string>
    <string name="run_test">Run test</string>
    <string name="dns_injection">DNS Injection</string>
    <string name="tcp_connect">TCP Connect</string>
    <string name="http_invalid_request_line">HTTP Invalid request line</string>
    <string name="http_header_field_manipulation">HTTP Header field manipulation</string>
    <string name="web_connectivity">Web Connectivity</string>
    <string name="ndt_test">Ndt Test</string>
    <string name="check_port">Check port</string>
    <string name="traceroute">Traceroute</string>
    <string name="running_tests">Running tests</string>
    <string name="finished_tests">Finished tests</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="collector_address">Collector Address</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="test_result">Test result</string>
    <string name="change">Change</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="wrong">Your answers to one or more of the quiz questions is wrong. Please read the Risks documentation and try again.</string>
    <string name="correct">You answered to the quiz correctly. Carry on.</string>
    <string name="configure">Configure</string>
    <string name="ooniprobe_configured">Successfully configured ooniprobe. You are all set to go!</string>
    <string name="introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="risks">Risks</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz</string>
    <string name="configuration">Configuration</string>
    <string name="intro_text"><![CDATA[<h1>Greetings!</h1><p>It looks like this is the first time you are running ooniprobe!</p><p>Please take a minute to go through this setup wizard to help you getstarted in setting ooniprobe. </p><p>We promise it won\'t take more than just a couple of minutes!</p><p>The Open Observatory of Network Interference (OONI) is a free software project, under the Tor Project, which collects and processes network measurements with the aim of detecting network anomalies, such as censorship and traffic manipulation.</p><p>Running OONI\'s software tests can potentially be a <strong>risky</strong> activity, depending on the laws and jurisdition of the country that you are running them from. This also largely depends on which tests you run and on which URLs you test. Please read this document carefully to understand more about the risks related to the use of ooniprobe.</p><span> By running ooniprobe, you are participating as a volunteer in this project. This form includes information that you should be aware of and consent to *prior* to running ooniprobe.]]></string>
    <string name="risks_text"><![CDATA[<h2>Risks</h2><p>Many countries have a lengthy history of subjecting digital rights activists to various forms of abuse that could make it dangerous for individuals in these countries to run ooniprobe. The use of ooniprobe might therefore subject users to severe civil, criminal, or extra-judicial penalties, and such sanctions can potentially include:</p><ul><li>Imprisonment</li><li>Physical assaults</li><li>Large fines</li><li>Receiving threats</li><li>Being placed on government watch lists</li><li>Targeted for surveillance</li></ul><p>While most countries don\'t have laws which specifically prohibit the use of network measurement software, it\'s important to note that the use of ooniprobe can <strong>still</strong> potentially be criminalized in certain countries under other, broader laws if, for example, its use is viewed as an illegal or anti-government activity. OONI users might also face the risk of being criminalized on the grounds of <strong>national security</strong> if the data obtained and published by running ooniprobe is viewed as \"jeopardizing\" the country\'s external or internal security. In extreme cases, any form of active network measurement could be illegal, or even considered a form of espionage. </p><p>We therefore strongly urge you to consult with lawyers <em>prior</em> to running ooniprobe. You can also reach out to us with specific inquiries at <strong>contact@openobservatory.org</strong>. Please note though that we are <em>not</em> lawyers, but we might be able to seek legal advice for you or to put you in touch with lawyers who could address your questions and/or concerns.</p><p>Some relevant resources include:</p><ul>  <li><a href=\"https://www.eff.org/torchallenge/faq.html\">Tor Legal FAQ</a></li>  <li>    <a href=\"https://www.eff.org/issues/know-your-rights\">EFF Know Your Rights</a>  </li></ul><p></p><p><strong>Note:</strong> The use of ooniprobe is at your <em>own risk</em> in accordance to OONI\'s software <a href=\"https://github.com/TheTorProject/ooni-probe/blob/master/LICENSE\">license</a> and neither the OONI project nor its parent organization, the Tor Project, can be held liable.</p><strong>Installing ooniprobe</strong><p>As with any other software, the usage of ooniprobe can leave traces. As such, anybody with physical or remote access to your computer might be able to see that you have downloaded, installed or run OONI.</p><p>The installation of <a href=\"https://www.torproject.org/\">Tor</a> software, which is designed for online anonymity, is a <em>prerequisite</em> for using ooniprobe as measurements are sent to OONI over Tor. Furthermore, OONI\'s Web Connectivity test is designed to compare HTTP requests over the network of the user and over the Tor network. Similarly, OONI\'s Psiphon, Lantern and OpenVPN tests require the installation of other circumvention software.</p><p>We therefore encourage you to consult with a lawyer on the legality of anonymity software (such as Tor, a VPN or a proxy) *prior* to installing ooniprobe.</p><p>To remove traces of software usage, you can re-install your operating system or wipe your computer and remove everything (operating system, programs and files) from your hard drive.</p><strong>Running ooniprobe</strong><p>Third parties (such as your government, ISP and/or employer) monitoring your internet activity will be able to see all web traffic generated by ooniprobe, including your IP address, and might be able to link it to you personally.</p><p>Many countries employ sophisticated surveillance measures that allow governments to track individuals\' online activities – even if they are using a VPN or a proxy server to protect their privacy. In such countries, governments might be able to identify you as a OONI user regardless of what measures you take to protect your online privacy.</p><strong>Testing URLs for censorship</strong><p>When running OONI\'s <strong>Web Connectivity</strong> or <strong>HTTP requests</strong> test, you will connect to and download data from various websites which are included in the following two lists:</p><ul><li>  <strong>Country-specific test list:</strong> https://github.com/citizenlab/test-lists/tree/master/lists (search for your country\'s test list based on its country code)</li><li>  <strong>Global test list:</strong> https://github.com/citizenlab/test-lists/blob/master/lists/global.csv (including a list of globally accessed websites)</li></ul><p>Many websites included in the above lists will likely be controversial and can include pornography or hate speech, which might be illegal to access in your country. We therefore recommend that you examine carefully whether you are willing to take the risk of accessing and downloading data from such websites through OONI tests, especially if this could potentially lead to various forms of retribution.</p><p>If you are uncertain of the potential implications of connecting to and downloading data from the websites listed in the above lists, you can choose which URLs to test via OONI\'s Web User Interface (WUI).</p><strong>Publication of measurements</strong><p>The public (including third parties who view the usage of OONI as illegal or \"suspicious\") will be able to see the information collected by OONI once it\'s published through:</p><ul><li><a href=\"https://explorer.ooni.torproject.org/world/\">OONI Explorer</a></li><li>  <a href=\"https://measurements.ooni.torproject.org/\">  OONI\'s list of measurements  </a></li></ul><p>Unless you <strong>opt-out</strong> through the configuration options of OONI\'s WUI, all measurements that are generated through OONI tests are by default sent to OONI\'s measurement collector and automatically published through the above resources.</p><p>Published data will include your approximate location, the network (ASN) you are connecting from, and when you ran ooniprobe. Other identifying information, such as your IP address, is <em>not</em> deliberately collected, but might be included in HTTP headers or other metadata. The full page content downloaded by OONI could potentially include further information if, for example, a website includes tracking codes or custom content based on your network location. Such information could potentially aid third parties in detecting you as an ooniprobe user.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="quiz_text">Please answer the following questions to ensure you have understood what ooniprobe does and that you are aware of risks associated with running the software.</string>
    <string name="quiz_test"><![CDATA[<h2>Quiz</h2><p>Please answer the following questions to ensure you have understood what ooniprobe does and that you are aware of risks associated with running the software.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="configuration_text">Certain aspects of how ooniprobe operates can be customized. Usually the default values are the best option, so only change these if you really have to.</string>
    <string name="configuration_test"><![CDATA[<h2>Configuration</h2><p>Certain aspects of how ooniprobe operates can be customized. Usually the default values are the best option, so only change these if you really have to.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="header_1">In regards to how detectable ooniprobe is, which of the following statements is true?</string>
    <string name="answer_1_1">Anyone monitoring my internet activity (e.g. ISP, government or employer) might be able to see that I am running ooniprobe, even though OONI takes precautions to make this hard</string>
    <string name="answer_1_2">Anyone monitoring my internet activity (e.g. ISP, government or employer) will not be able to see that I am running ooniprobe</string>
    <string name="answer_1_3">ooniprobe is designed to protect my privacy and therefore my use of ooniprobe cannot be detected</string>
    <string name="header_2">In regards to the publication of measurements, which of the following statements is true?</string>
    <string name="answer_2_1">My measurements will not by default get published on OONI Explorer</string>
    <string name="answer_2_2">My measurements will by default get published on OONI Explorer and might include personally-identifiable information.</string>
    <string name="answer_2_3">My measurements will by default get published to OONI Explorer and will never include any personally-identifiable information</string>
    <string name="include_ip">Should we include your IP address in results?</string>
    <string name="include_asn">Should we include your network information in the reports (note: disabling this will make it much harder for us to draw conclusions from the measurements)?</string>
    <string name="include_cc">Should we include your country name in the reports (note: disabling this will make it much harder for us to draw conclusions from the measurements)?</string>
    <string name="upload_results">Should we upload your results to the default ooni collector?</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
</resources>
